A Guide to the John D. Rockefeller 3rd papers FA108
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Office of the Messrs. Rockefeller Files, 1906-1969 1906-1961; 1; 34.5 Cubic Feet 98 Boxes
  - Lincoln Center, 1955-1969 1955-1966; 4
    - Printed Material - "Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts" (hardcover), 1960 (Box 79, Folder 666B)
    - Lincoln Center plans: Acquisition of property and Federal support, Quantity: 10 (Box Cabinet B Drawer 2, Folder 100)
  - Population Interests, 1951-1967 1951-1961; 5
    John D. Rockefeller 3rd developed an interest in the topic of population during his work for the Bureau of Social Hygiene. Rockefeller, who in speeches consistently linked population control to quality of life, became an acknowledged world leader in combating overpopulation. In addition to the files that reveal Rockefeller's general concern regarding the population issue (folders 667-670), this subseries documents the 1951 Conference on Population Problems (folders 718-723) held at Colonial Williamsburg, which was convened by Rockefeller and led to the founding of the Population Council, Inc., a year later. The subseries also sheds light on the early work of the Population Council, an organization founded by Rockefeller to fund biological and demographic research and training fellowships.
    - General, 1952-1961 (Box 80, Folder 667)
    - General, 1952-1961 (Box 80, Folder 668)
    - General, 1952-1961 (Box 80, Folder 669)
    - General, 1952-1961 (Box 80, Folder 670)
    - Japan - Birth Control, 1951-1960 (Box 80, Folder 671)
    - Japan - Birth Control - Printed Material, 1949-1952, 1953, 1959 (Box 80, Folder 672)
    - Japan - Birth Control - Printed Material, 1949-1952, 1953, 1959 (Box 80, Folder 673)
    - Population Council, Inc. - General, 1952-1958 (Box 81, Folder 674)
    - Population Council, Inc. - General, 1952-1958 (Box 81, Folder 675)
    - Population Council, Inc. - General, 1952-1958 (Box 81, Folder 676)
    - Population Council, Inc. - General, 1952-1958 (Box 81, Folder 677)
    - Population Council, Inc. - General, 1952-1958 (Box 81, Folder 678)
    - Population Council, Inc. - General, 1952-1958 (Box 81, Folder 679)
    - Population Council, Inc. - General, 1959-1965 (Box 82, Folder 680)
    - Population Council, Inc. - General, 1959-1965 (Box 82, Folder 681)
    - Population Council, Inc. - Bylaws and Certificate of Incorporation, 1952 (Box 82, Folder 682)
    - Population Council, Inc. - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1952-1953 (Box 82, Folder 683)
    - Population Council, Inc. - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1954 (Box 82, Folder 684)
    - Population Council, Inc. - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1955 (Box 82, Folder 685)
    - Population Council, Inc. - Board of Trustees Meetings, January 18, 1956 (Box 82, Folder 686)
    - Population Council, Inc. - Board of Trustees Meetings, May 9, 1956 (Box 82, Folder 687)
    - Population Council, Inc. - Board of Trustees Meetings, October 30, 1956 (Box 82, Folder 688)
    - Population Council, Inc. - Board of Trustees Meetings, January 10, 1957 (Box 82, Folder 689)
    - Population Council, Inc. - Board of Trustees Meetings, April 5, 1957 (Box 82, Folder 690)
    - Population Council, Inc. - Board of Trustees Meetings, October 3, 1957 (Box 82, Folder 691)
    - Population Council, Inc. - Board of Trustees Meetings, January 16, 1958 (Box 82, Folder 692)
    - Population Council, Inc. - Board of Trustees Meetings, May 16, 1958 (Box 83, Folder 693)
    - Population Council, Inc. - Board of Trustees Meetings, November 13, 1958 (Box 83, Folder 694)
    - Population Council, Inc. - Board of Trustees Meetings, January 21, 1959 (Box 83, Folder 695)
    - Population Council, Inc. - Board of Trustees Meetings, May 13, 1959 (Box 83, Folder 696)
    - Population Council, Inc. - Board of Trustees Meetings, October 14, 1959 (Box 83, Folder 697)
    - Population Council, Inc. - Board of Trustees Meetings, January 6, 1960 (Box 83, Folder 698)
    - Population Council, Inc. - Board of Trustees Meetings, April 5, 1960 (Box 83, Folder 699)
    - Population Council, Inc. - Board of Trustees Meetings, January 11, 1961 (Box 83, Folder 700)
    - Population Council, Inc. - Board of Trustees Meetings, May 8, 1961 (Box 83, Folder 701)
    - Population Council, Inc. - Board of Trustees Meetings, October 25, 1961 (Box 83, Folder 702)
    - Population Council, Inc. - Board of Trustees Meetings, December 20, 1961 (Box 84, Folder 703)
    - Population Council, Inc. - Contributions, 1954-1962 (Box 84, Folder 704)
    - Population Council, Inc. - Finances and Securities, 1953, 1961 (Box 84, Folder 705)
    - Population Council, Inc. - Grants, 1953-1962 (Box 84, Folder 706)
    - Population Council, Inc. - Letters of Appeal, 1957 (Box 84, Folder 707)
    - Population Council, Inc. - Meetings, 1954-1962 (Box 84, Folder 708)
    - Population Council, Inc. - Personnel (CLOSED FOLDER), 1952-1953, 1955-1959, 1961-1967 (Box 84, Folder 709)
    - Population Council, Inc. - Personnel (CLOSED FOLDER), 1952-1953, 1955-1959, 1961-1967 (Box 84, Folder 710)
    - Population Council, Inc. - Personnel (CLOSED FOLDER), 1952-1953, 1955-1959, 1961-1967 (Box 84, Folder 711)
    - Population Council, Inc. - Personnel (CLOSED FOLDER), 1952-1953, 1955-1959, 1961-1967 (Box 84, Folder 712)
    - Population Council, Inc. - Population Investigation Committee, 1952-1953 (Box 85, Folder 713)
    - Population Council, Inc. - President, selection of, 1958-1959 (Box 85, Folder 714)
    - Population Council, Inc. - Publicity, 1953, 1954, 1961 (Box 85, Folder 715)
    - Population Council, Inc. - Reports, 1955-1960 (Box 85, Folder 716)
    - Population Council, Inc. - Rockefeller Institute, 1955-1961 (Box 85, Folder 717)
    - Population Council, Inc. - Williamsburg Conference - Documentation, 1952 (Box 85, Folder 718)
    - Population Council, Inc. - Williamsburg Conference - Documentation, 1952 (Box 85, Folder 719)
    - Population Council, Inc. - Williamsburg Conference - Sessions, 1952 (Box 85, Folder 720)
    - Population Council, Inc. - Williamsburg Conference - Sessions, 1952 (Box 85, Folder 721)
    - Population Council, Inc. - Williamsburg Conference - Sessions, 1952 (Box 85, Folder 722)
    - Population Council, Inc. - Williamsburg Conference - Sessions, 1952 (Box 85, Folder 723)
  - Trips, 1920-1960; 6
    Arranged chronologically.
    Beginning with his family's trip to the western United States in 1920, Rockefeller kept accounts of each day's activities in travel logs and diaries. Of note in this subseries are Rockefeller's record of his college graduation world tour in 1929 (folders 728-731); his General Education Board field trips, 1940-1947 (folders 733-734); and the trips to Europe, the Far East, and Africa undertaken on behalf of the Rockefeller Foundation. The field trips undertaken with other GEB trustees involved a study of poverty, race relations, and education in the rural South, notably Georgia, Mississippi, and Arkansas. Also documented here are Rockefeller's annual mid-winter visits to Asia, which began in 1951. With his travels, Rockefeller intended to gain firsthand knowledge of a region's economic and social conditions. To that end, he traveled extensively in Asia, Europe, and Africa. His diaries and logs contain observations on the cultures, societies, and people of the various countries he visited.
    - General, 1935-1962 (Box 86, Folder 724)
      - Trips - General (Box P 170, Folder 16)
    - United States (1920) - Diary (Box 86, Folder 725)
    - Europe (1926), 1925-1927 (Box 86, Folder 726)
    - Geneva (1928) (Box 86, Folder 727)
    - World Tour (1929), 1928-1931 (Box 86, Folder 728)
    - World Tour (1929) - Book 1, 1928-1931 (Box 86, Folder 729)
    - World Tour (1929) - Book 2, 1928-1931 (Box 86, Folder 730)
    - World Tour (1929) - Book 3, 1928-1931 (Box 86, Folder 731)
    - Europe (1933) (Box 87, Folder 732)
    - General Education Board Field Trips, 1940-1947 (Box 87, Folder 733)
      - GEB Trip, 1940-1941 (Box P 170, Folder 17)
    - General Education Board Field Trips, 1940-1947 (Box 87, Folder 734)
    - Europe (1946) (Box 87, Folder 735)
    - Europe (1946) - Diary (Box 87, Folder 736)
    - Orient (1947), 1947-1949 (Box 87, Folder 737)
    - Orient (1947), 1947-1949 (Box 87, Folder 738)
    - Orient (1947) (A-M), 1947-1949 (Box 87, Folder 739)
    - Orient (1947) (N-Z), 1947-1949 (Box 88, Folder 740)
    - Orient (1947) - Japan - Diary, 1947-1949 (Box 88, Folder 741)
    - Orient (1947) - Korea - Diary, 1947-1949 (Box 88, Folder 742)
    - Orient (1947) - Japan, China, and Korea - Notebook, 1947-1949 (Box 88, Folder 743)
    - Africa (1948) (Box 88, Folder 744)
      - Africa, 1948 (Box P 170, Folder 18)
    - Africa (1948) (Box 88, Folder 745)
    - Africa (1948) (Box 88, Folder 746)
    - Africa (1948) (Box 88, Folder 747)
    - Africa (1948) - Countries (Box 89, Folder 748)
    - Africa (1948) - Countries - Miscellaneous Letters, 1948-1950 (Box 89, Folder 749)
    - Africa (1948) - Countries - Miscellaneous Letters, 1948-1950 (Box 89, Folder 750)
    - Africa (1948) - Countries - Miscellaneous Letters, 1948-1950 (Box 89, Folder 751)
    - Africa (1948) - Notebook (Box 89, Folder 752)
    - Africa (1948) - Belgian Congo - Diary (Box 89, Folder 753)
    - Africa (1948) - Kenya and Ethiopia - Diary (Box 89, Folder 754)
    - Africa (1948) - Liberia, Gold Coast, and Nigeria - Diary (Box 89, Folder 755)
    - Africa (1948) - South Africa - Diary (Box 89, Folder 756)
    - Europe (1950) (Box 90, Folder 757)
    - Europe (1950) - France and England - Diary (Box 90, Folder 758)
    - Japan (c. 1951) - Notebook (Box 90, Folder 759)
    - Japan (January-February 1951) - Diary (Box 90, Folder 760)
    - Japan (January-February 1951) - Notebook (Box 90, Folder 761)
    - Japan (January-February 1951), 1949-1953 (Box 90, Folder 762)
    - Mexico and Colombia (July-August 1951) (Box 90, Folder 763)
    - Mexico and Colombia (July-August 1951) - Diary (Box 90, Folder 764)
    - Japan (October-November 1951) (Box 90, Folder 765)
    - Japan (October-November 1951) - Diary (Box 91, Folder 766)
    - Japan (April 1952) - Diary (Box 91, Folder 767)
    - Japan (April 1952) - Notebook (Box 91, Folder 768)
    - Japan (April 1952), 1951-1952 (Box 91, Folder 769)
    - Europe (June 1952) (Box 91, Folder 770)
    - Asia (1953) (Box 91, Folder 771)
    - Asia (1953) (Box 91, Folder 772)
    - Asia (1953) - Countries (B-J), (P-Z) (Box 91, Folder 773)
    - Asia (1953) - Countries (B-J), (P-Z) (Box 91, Folder 774)
    - Asia (1953) - Diary (Box 91, Folder 775)
    - Asia (1953) - Diary (Box 91, Folder 776)
    - Asia (1953) - Notebook (Box 92, Folder 777)
    - Asia (1954), 1953-1954 (Box 92, Folder 778)
    - Asia (1954) - Conversations (Box 92, Folder 779)
    - Asia (1954) - Countries (Box 92, Folder 780)
    - Asia (1954) - Diaries (Box 92, Folder 781)
    - Asia (1954) - Diaries (Box 92, Folder 782)
    - Asia (1954) - India, Pakistan, and Singapore - Notebook (Box 92, Folder 783)
    - Asia (1954) - Indonesia and Japan - Notebook (Box 92, Folder 784)
    - Asia (January 1955) (Postponed) (Box 92, Folder 785)
    - Asia (June-August 1955), 1955-1956 (Box 92, Folder 786)
      - Trips - Asia, 1955 (Box P 170, Folder 19)
    - Asia (June-August 1955) - Notebook, 1955-1956 (Box 93, Folder 787)
    - Asia (June-August 1955) - Diary, 1955-1956 (Box 93, Folder 788)
    - Europe (1956) (Box 93, Folder 789)
    - Europe (1956) - Diary (Box 93, Folder 790)
    - Southeast Asia (January-March 1957), 1957-1958 (Box 93, Folder 791)
      - Southeast Asia, 1957 (Box P 170, Folder 20)
    - Southeast Asia (January-March 1957) - Countries (Box 93, Folder 792)
    - Southeast Asia (January-March 1957) - Countries (Box 93, Folder 793)
    - Southeast Asia (January-March 1957) - Diary (Box 93, Folder 794)
    - Southeast Asia (January-March 1957) - Notebook (Box 93, Folder 795)
    - Far East (June-August 1957), 1957-1958 (Box 93, Folder 796)
    - Far East (June-August 1957) - Countries (Box 93, Folder 797)
    - Far East (June-August 1957) - Diary (Box 94, Folder 798)
    - Far East (June-August 1957) - Notebook (Box 94, Folder 799)
    - Asia (1958) (Box 94, Folder 800)
    - Asia (1958) - Countries (Box 94, Folder 801)
    - Asia (1958) - Japan (Box 94, Folder 802)
    - Asia (1958) - Diary (Box 94, Folder 803)
    - Asia (1958) - Notebook (Box 94, Folder 804)
    - Philippines (Summer 1958) (Box 94, Folder 805)
    - Philippines (Summer 1958) - Diary (Box 94, Folder 806)
    - Far East (1959) (Box 94, Folder 807)
    - Far East (1959) - Countries (Box 94, Folder 808)
    - Far East (1959) - Diary (Box 95, Folder 809)
    - Far East (1959) - Notebook (Box 95, Folder 810)
    - Japan (1959) (Box 95, Folder 811)
    - Europe (1959) (Box 95, Folder 812)
    - Europe (1959) - Diary (Box 95, Folder 813)
    - Europe (1960) - Diary (Box 95, Folder 814)
    - Far East (1960) (Box 95, Folder 815)
    - Far East (1960) - Books 1 and 2 (Box 95, Folder 816)
    - Far East (1960) - Books 1 and 2 (Box 95, Folder 817)
    - Far East (1960) - Diary (Box 95, Folder 818)
    - Far East (1960) - Notebook (Box 95, Folder 819)
    - Miscellany (Box P 170, Folder 21)
  - Financial Material, 1930-1961; 7
    This subserires consists of annual and cumulative financial reports prepared by family associates, most notably Arthur W. Packard and Dana Creel, that document Rockefeller's charitable contributions from 1932 to 1961. The subseries also contains Packard's charitable corporations activities reviews for 1943 to 1946.
    For information on contributions in later years, see series 3, subseries 9.
    - Contributions - General, 1937-1961 (Box 96, Folder 820)
    - Contributions - Benevolences, 1932-1961 (Box 96, Folder 821)
    - Contributions - Program, 1950-1960 (Box 96, Folder 822)
    - Contributions - Program, 1950-1960 (Box 96, Folder 823)
    - Contributions - Program, 1950-1960 (Box 96, Folder 824)
    - Contributions - Program, 1950-1960 (Box 96, Folder 825)
    - Contributions - Program, 1950-1960 (Box 96, Folder 826)
    - Contributions - Program, 1950-1960 (Box 96, Folder 827)
    - Contributions - Program, 1950-1960 (Box 96, Folder 828)
    - Contributions - Program, 1950-1960 (Box 96, Folder 829)
    - Contributions - Program, 1950-1960 (Box 96, Folder 830)
    - Contributions - Program, 1950-1960 (Box 96, Folder 831)
    - Contributions - Program, 1950-1960 (Box 96, Folder 832)
    - Contributions - Program, 1961 (Box 97, Folder 833)
    - Contributions - Reports, 1937-1941 (Box 97, Folder 834)
    - Contributions - Reports, 1942-1946 (Box 97, Folder 835)
    - Contributions - Reports - Packard (Arthur W.), Boards and Committees, 1943-1946 (Box 97, Folder 836)
    - Contributions - Reports, 1947-1948 (Box 97, Folder 837)
    - Contributions - Reports, 1951-1954 (Box 97, Folder 838)
    - Contributions - Reports, 1955-1958 (Box 97, Folder 839)
    - Contributions - Reports, 1958-1961 (Box 98, Folder 840)
    - Contributions - Reports - Cumulative, 1930-1960 (Box 98, Folder 841)
    - Contributions - Reports - Cumulative, 1930-1960 (Box 98, Folder 842)
- Rockefeller Family and Associates Files, 1942-1977 1962-1977; 2; 17.5 Cubic Feet 51 Boxes
  The original filing order created in the Rockefeller family office has been maintained for this subseries. General correspondence, 1962-1976, is filed before the alphabetical subject sequence.
  Chronological correspondence from 1962 to 1969 (folders 206-298), which consists of copies of Rockefeller's outgoing correspondence, includes letters that Rockefeller wrote in his capacity as chairman of Lincoln Center. This series documents Rockefeller's work for the U.S. Bicentennial, including his efforts on behalf of the National Committee for the Bicentennial, as well as awards received (1942-1976) and trips taken (1962-1976). It also contains reading copies and drafts of speeches given (folders 45-123) and statements made (folders 367-371) by Rockefeller between 1964 and 1976. In this series, speeches are filed under "Addresses." The Statements files include JDR 3rd's testimony before Rep. Wright Patman's House Ways and Means Committee during hearings on the 1969 Tax Reform Bill (folder 367-368). In his testimony, Rockefeller offered his views on the impact the new tax proposals would have on the state of philanthropy. Newspaper and magazine articles written by and about Rockefeller will be found here, as will information regarding purchases and prospective additions to his art collection (filed under "Works of Art," folders 402-438). Other topics covered in this series include public relations; radio and television appearances; real estate properties; invitations to speak; and invitations to attend dinners, luncheons, and receptions.
  Additional and overlapping material on Rockefeller's speeches can be found in series 3, subseries 6. For additional material on the 1969 Tax Reform Bill, see "Tax Reform" files in series 3, subseries 3, box 62, folders 399-402.
  - General Correspondence (A), 1962-1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence (A), 1962-1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence (B), 1962-1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence (B), 1962-1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence (B), 1962-1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence (C), 1962-1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence (C), 1962-1976 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence (D), 1962-1976 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence (D), 1962-1976 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence (E), 1962-1976 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence (E), 1962-1976 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence (F-G), 1962-1976 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence (F-G), 1962-1976 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence (F-G), 1962-1976 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence (H-J), 1962-1976 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - H (Box P 171, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence (H-J), 1962-1976 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - General Correspondence (I-J), 1962-1976 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - General Correspondence (K-L), 1962-1976 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - K (Box P 171, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence (K-L), 1962-1976 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - General Correspondence (K-L), 1962-1976 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - General Correspondence (K-L), 1962-1976 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - General Correspondence (K-L), 1962-1976 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - General Correspondence (M), 1962-1976 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - M (Box P 171, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence (M), 1962-1976 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - General Correspondence (M), 1962-1976 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - General Correspondence (M), 1962-1976 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - General Correspondence (M), 1962-1976 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - General Correspondence (N), 1962-1976 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - N (Box P 171, Folder 4)
    - N (Box P 171, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence (N), 1962-1976 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - General Correspondence (O), 1962-1976 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - General Correspondence (O-P), 1962-1976 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - General Correspondence (O-P), 1962-1976 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - General Correspondence (O-P), 1962-1976 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - General Correspondence (Q-R), 1962-1976 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - R (Box P 171, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence (Q-R), 1962-1976 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - General Correspondence (Q-R), 1962-1976 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - General Correspondence (S), 1962-1976 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - General Correspondence (S-T), 1962-1976 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - General Correspondence (S-T), 1962-1976 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - General Correspondence (S-T), 1962-1976 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - T (Box P 171, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence (U-W), 1962-1976 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - U (Box P 171, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence (U-W), 1962-1976 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - General Correspondence (Y), 1962-1976 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Accident, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Addresses - Aichi (Kiichi) Dinner, September 16, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Addresses - Americas Foundation, October 10, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Addresses - Arts and Education Council of Greater St. Louis, April 17, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Addresses - Asia Society, May 16, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Addresses - Asia Society, February 24, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Addresses - Asia Society, May 28, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Asia Society, 1970 May 28 (Box P 171, Folder 9)
  - Addresses - Association for the Study of Abortion, November 18, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Addresses - Association for the Study of Abortion, November 18, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Addresses - Bicentennial Commission, January 20, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Addresses - "Changing Values for a New America", October 1971 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Addresses - Citizens Involvement Network, September 17, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Addresses - Commission on Private Philanthropy and Public Needs (Filer Commission), December 2, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Addresses - Concord Academy, April 17-18, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Addresses - Conference Board, February 24, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Addresses - Conference Board, February 24, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Addresses - Council on Foreign Relations, October 2, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Addresses - Damrosch Park (Lincoln Center) Dedication, May 22, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Addresses - First Pennsylvania Corporation, November 21, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Addresses - Guttmacher (Alan) Memorial Service, April 18, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Addresses - Hampshire College, December 6, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Addresses - Hampshire College, December 6, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Addresses - Harvard Club (Shimoda Luncheon), August 27, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Addresses - International House (New York City), November 9, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Addresses - International House of Japan, May 14, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Addresses - International House of Japan, November 14, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Addresses - International Institute of Education, October 28, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Addresses - Japan Society (Japan House Groundbreaking), September 16, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Addresses - Japan Society (William P. Rogers Dinner), June 30, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Addresses - Japan Society (Japan House Dedication), September 13, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Addresses - Japan Society, May 21, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Addresses - Japan Society, August 7, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Addresses - Japan Society (Japan House Reception), October 6, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Addresses - Juilliard School, October 26, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Addresses - Lincoln Center Luncheon, May 2, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 78)
    - 1967 May 2 (Box P 171, Folder 10)
  - Addresses - Lincoln Center, June 23, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Addresses - Loomis-Chaffee School, June 7, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - Addresses - McCray (Porter) Reception, September 3, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - Addresses - Michigan State University, May 1975 (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - Addresses - National Academy of Television Arts and Sciences, March 15, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - Addresses - National Committee on United States-China Relations, March 20, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 84)
  - Addresses - National Institute of Social Sciences, November 28, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - Addresses - New York City Board of Education, May 7, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - Addresses - Planned Parenthood Federation of America, January 13, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - Addresses - Planned Parenthood-World Population, October 19, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Addresses - Press Foundation of Asia, April 12, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - Addresses - Press Foundation of Asia, April 12, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - Addresses - Princeton University - Rockefeller Public Service Awards, 1967-1969 (Box 10, Folder 91)